cegeka.com 2018-09-02

# Privacy Policy - Cegeka

This website is operated by Cegeka nv, a company incorporated under Belgian law, having its registered office in Hasselt with company registration number 0882.419.490. Cegeka nv forms part of Cegeka Groep, a Belgian corporation with several branches spread over different European Union Member States.

Cegeka is a company that is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Notice explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use our website [www.cegeka.com](http://www.cegeka.com/?hsLang=en) (or [www.nsi-sa.be](http://www.nsi-sa.be/?hsLang=en)) or when we do or may do business with each other.

## What information do we collect about you?

Cegeka collects information about you when you use the functionality offered on or through this website to (i) request a meeting, (ii) ask a question through the contact form, (iii) download certain content, such as white papers, (iv) register for an event, or (v) submit your CV and other data on our job page. This information is usually limited to contact details, like your name, place of residence, email address, telephone number, company name and position. Additional data may be requested in specific cases, for example in case of an online application.

We will also collect information about you when you voluntarily complete surveys, such as customer satisfaction surveys or feedback on our website

Website usage information like e.g. your IP address, date and duration of your visit to this website, your browser and your navigation on this website, is collected by using cookies. Further information on the use of cookies is provided in our [Cookie Policy](https://www.cegeka.com/en/cookie-statement?hsLang=en).

You may also provide this information to Cegeka to perform a contract as a customer, as a supplier or business partner.

## How will we use the information about you?

Cegeka collects information about you to handle your questions, requests and applications and, if you agree, to collect personal statistical information. Cegeka wil use the information you provide to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into by you and us. We may also send you newsletters and personalized marketing by email. We also use your information collected from this website to personalize your visits to our website.

## Who has access to your information?

We will not share your information for marketing purposes with companies outside the Cegeka Group.

We may pass your information to our third party service providers, agents subcontractors and other associated organizations for the purposes of completing tasks, providing services to you or performing a contract that we have entered into. However, when we use third party service providers, we disclose only the information that is necessary to deliver the service and we have a contract in place that requires them to keep your information secure and not to use it for their own direct marketing purposes.

## Why do we use information about you?

Cegeka collects and processes this information from you on the basis of any of the following legal bases:

**Legal basis**

| 

**Description**  
  
---|---  
  
Contractual

| 

The processing is necessary to perform a contract with you.  
  
Legal obligation

| 

The processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which Cegeka is subject.  
  
Legitimate interest

| 

The processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by Cegeka or by a third party, provided that your interests or fundamental rights and freedoms do not prevail.  
  
Consent

| 

You have given your consent to the processing of your personal data.  
  
Remarks:

  * “ _Contractual_ ” is not limited to a signed contract, e.g. performing the recruitment process is performing a contract between the candidate and Cegeka; and delivering an e-book, requested by you, is also considered performing a contract between you and Cegeka.

  * “ _Legitimate interest_ ” may be used where you may reasonably expect that your personal data will be stored and used, e.g.: 
    * When you leave your contact details when downloading an e-book on a certain topic, you can reasonably expect Cegeka to store your interest in that topic in order to share other, relevant information on similar topics with you.
    * When you ask a question on the contact form on a certain topic, you might reasonably expect that an expert on that topic will contact you to further discuss your question.

## Marketing

Cegeka would like to send you information about its products and services which may be of interest to you. Cegeka may also contact you in connection with our customer satisafaction survey program.

You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your information to other companies within the Cegeka Group.

If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, you can opt-out via the latest e-mail you received from us. Do not hesitate to contact [marketing@cegeka.com](mailto:marketing@cegeka.com) for further information and questions.

## How can you access and correct your information?

You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all or your personal information, please send us an email or write to us at the address referred to below.

Cegeka also wants to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct information you think is inaccurate, or request us to remove your information.

## How long do we store your data?

Cegeka will not store your information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which we need this information about you. However, it is also important to note that, in some cases, we will be legally required to keep your information for a certain amount of time.

## Security measures

When you give Cegeka your personal information, we take steps to ensure that it is treated securely. Cegeka has implemented reasonable physical, organizational and technical measures to help protect your personal information against unauthorized access, disclosure or use.

## Complaints

If you feel that Cegeka is processing your personal data unlawfully or incorrectly, please do not hesitate to contact us via the contact details mentioned below.

In any event, you always have a right to file a complaint to the authority responsible for data protection in your country, if you are of the opinion that your information has not been processed correctly by Cegeka.

## Cookies and Terms of Use

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website, to improve website experience and to compile statistical reports on website activity.

You will find further information on the use of cookies in our [Cookie Policy.](https://www.cegeka.com/en/cookie-statement?hsLang=en)

You will find a description of the conditions for your use of this website in the [Terms and Conditions.](https://www.cegeka.com/en/terms-and-conditions?hsLang=en)

## Changes to our privacy notice

Cegeka reserves the right to amend this Privacy Notice from time to time. We will place any updates thereof on this website. This Privacy Notice was last modified and revised on May 3rd 2018.

## How to contact us

If you have any questions about the processing of your personal data, or regarding this Privacy Notice, you can contact Cegeka at the following address:

Cegeka NV  
Universiteitslaan 9  
B – 3500 Hasselt
